https://www.bgfashion.net/privacy-policy.php

Skip to content
BGFN MAGAZINE >> Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy of
Be Global Fashion Network (BGFN)
1. Methods of processing
This page describes the methods by which Fashion.bg Ltd. provides for the processing of personal data of the users of its websites, including customers who have signed a contract with the company, so that each user is able to express a free and informed consent to the processing of their data. This Privacy Notice is made pursuant to and by the effects of the d. lgs. 196/03 (Code regarding the protection of personal data or Code) and relates to the services offered by Fashion.bg Ltd., also through its websites www.bgfashion.net , www.bgfashion.it, www.bgfashion.at, www.bgfashion.co.uk, www.fashion.bg.
The personal data of the users obtained from Fashion.bg Ltd. through the website registration, signing of a contract or otherwise, will be treated by our company, meditating on the use of electronic and automated tools, for all the purposes and needs specified in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Notice may be amended by Fashion.bg Ltd., also in order to take into account the legislative changes in the subject, the technological developments that have taken place and changes to the activities of our company. In this case, Fashion.bg Ltd. will communicate to customers
the presence of a new version of the Privacy Policy, providing extensive publicity on its sites.
Informed consent of users
By providing us with your personal data when creating an account on our site, signing to our newsletter or signing a contract, you expressly and voluntarily accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and consent to the processing of data by our company for the purposes indicated here. Failure to provide personal data does not entail any detrimental consequences for the user but does not allow us to provide the user with the service signed with the relevant contract or the data and information requested. The user data is intended for use within the company and may only be processed by employees and / or collaborators (for example, IT service providers for the management of our servers) for the purpose of the execution of the contract signed or the supply of the requested information. Any form of dissemination of user data is excluded. Users' personal data may be disclosed to third parties in the event that such communication is mandatory by law. Pursuant to art.130, paragraph 4 of the Code, our company may use without prior consent the e-mail coordinates of users provided during the signing of the contract or the request for a demo account or information material also to promote similar services services provided under the contract or to which the user has requested information. In any case, each user may at any time oppose the receipt of any promotional communication that may be sent for these purposes. Each user may express his refusal to receive further promotional communications related to the following address: office@bgfashion.net
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT
A. Information You Provide
I. Account Registration. When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, social network profiles, website and telephone number. This information is published in a company profile and made available on the internet.
II. Registration for weekly newsletter. When you subscribe to our newsletter you provide your name, email and profession (optional). This information is not shared to anyone else and is used just for the purpose of sending you a newsletter. You can opt-out from the newsletter at any time by clicking a link in the email sent from us.
III. Communications. If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, personal email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide. We may also receive a confirmation when you open an email from us.
The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.
B. Information We Collect When You Use Our Services.
I.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. In addition, when you use our Services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device.
This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, landing page, and referring URL. To collect this information, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Services. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognize you. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or clear gifs to record your preferences. We may also automatically collect information about your use of features of our Services, about the functionality of our Services, frequency of visits, and other information related to your interactions with the Services. We may track your use across different websites and services. In some countries, including countries in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), the information referenced above in this paragraph may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws.
2. HOW WE USE INFORMATION
We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:
Provide, operate, and maintain our Services;
Improve, personalize, and expand our Services;
Understand and analyze how you use our Services;
Develop new products, services, features, and functionality;
Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the Service, and for marketing and promotional purposes;
Process your transactions;
Send you text messages and push notifications;
Find and prevent fraud; and
For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service, or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency.
3. HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION
We may share the information we collect in various ways, including the following:
A. Sharing your information online. We share information about your company which you provided through the registration for the purpose of sharing and getting exposure on our site - free or paid.
B. Advertising. We work with third-party advertising partners to show you ads that we think may interest you. These advertising partners may set and access their own cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies on our Services, and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you which they may collect over time and across different online services. Some of our advertising partners are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance.
C. Third-Party Partners. We
share information about users with third-party partners which provide services to us, related to the use of the information you provided for the purpose of providing our services to you in the best possible way.
D. Analytics. We use analytics providers such as Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect non-identifying information. Google provides some additional privacy options regarding its Analytics cookies at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.
E. Business Transfers. Information may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to any potential acquirer, successor, or assignee as part of any proposed merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets.
As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures. We may also share information to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; (iv) respond to your requests; or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.
With Your Consent. We may share information with your consent.
4. LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.
However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you; (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights; or (iii) where we have your consent to do so.
We have a legitimate interest in operating our Services and communicating with you as necessary to provide these Services, for example when responding to your queries, improving our platform, undertaking marketing, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities.
In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).
4. Data made publicly available by users
The information, supplied through registration in Fashion.bg ltd. directory at https://www.bgfashion.net/directory/ is intended for publishing in a company profile and the registrant has the power to choose what information to provide and publish to the public. Fashion.bg ltd., through computer systems and / or software procedures implemented on its own sites, can automatically acquire information made publicly available by users on internet pages, such as blogs and social media. Fashion.bg ltd. considers the privacy of users very seriously, therefore the computer systems adopted by Fashion.bg ltd. collect only and exclusively the information that users have freely and publicly available on the Internet and in compliance with the access criteria provided in the site file. Even if publicly available, we never send email addresses to third parties.
5. User rights
Each user, including customers who have signed a contract with Fashion.bg ltd., can exercise the rights set forth in art. 7 of the Code (including the rights of access, rectification, updating, integration and deletion of data) by contacting the data controller, which is: Fashion.bg ltd., Bulgaria, Ruse, 52 Pliska Str., VAT BG117536637, email: office@bgfashion.net.
Copyright © 1999-2020 Fashion.bg Ltd. All rights reserved.
AdvertisementBECOME MEMBER
Be Global Fashion Network
Men's fashionNewsVideo
FABRIC DAYS Spring-Summer 2022 postponed to 2 – 4 March 2021
07 December, 2020
6 Simple Ways Men Can Look Stunning At Work
02 December, 2020
Can made-to-measure survive in the age of social distancing?
02 December, 2020
THE Laser is the new innovative, revolutionary laser line by Tonello
27 November, 2020
How advances in technology are driving the future of made-to-measure fashion and body measuring
27 November, 2020
Beat the odds: 3 secrets for MTM businesses to thrive amid challenging 2020
18 November, 2020
How clusters can strengthen the European economy in the textile sector
14 November, 2020
A revolutionary and sustainable digital textile dying machine NEXTIL
09 November, 2020
The German Institutes for Textile and Fibre Research to develop reusable medical face masks of precision woven fabric
09 November, 2020
Designers from the Russian capital presented their clothing collections at Futurum Moscow
Futurum Moscow: Fashion shows of emerging designers on October 3
02 October, 2020
The Best 4 Men’s Fashion Trends To Look Out For This Fall
30 September, 2020
First meeting of FASCINATE - Sustainable Fashion Alliance for International Markets
25 September, 2020
Autumn-Winter 2021/2022 fashion trends from Premiére Vision Paris
25 September, 2020
s’elections moscow 2020 presented collections for Spring/Summer 2021
Day of Moscow-based brands has opened Global Talents Digital
05 September, 2020
Fabric days from 1 - 3 September 2020
31 August, 2020
BORIS BECKER collection to be presented at Gallery FASHION & SHOES
24 August, 2020
Responding to Fashion Market Changes With On-Demand Technology
18 August, 2020
Why Vintage sunglasses are back on trend
16 August, 2020
Gallery FASHION & SHOES is bringing the industry back together in person
10 August, 2020
FABRIC DAYS will take place from 1 - 3 September 2020 in Munich
27 July, 2020
Pitti Connect - the digital platform that will host the Pitti summer fairs starts on 16 July
09 July, 2020
Gallery FASHION and Gallery SHOES - 30 August - 01 September 2020
08 July, 2020
Neonyt on Air to take place online from 13-17 July
06 July, 2020
RUCO®-BAC AGP: the fast-acting, all-in-one, highly durable antibacterial and antiviral solution for textiles
30 June, 2020
Win one of the 30 Scholarships for 2021 Master Courses in Fashion, Design, Communication and, Photography at Raffles Milano
26 November, 2020
SWISS ARABIAN perfumes and perfume oils - A legacy that spans almost half a century
26 November, 2020
New study shows that managers are more positive now about flexible working and staff working from home
23 November, 2020
Milano Green Forum aims to increase environmental awareness
18 November, 2020
AEI Téxtils participated in the European Cluster Conference 2020
16 November, 2020
Support for female garment workers is crucial
12 November, 2020
First virtual European Cluster Conference 2020 discussing priorities for cluster policies and developments
10 November, 2020
Custom Menswear Designer Inherent Clothier Partners Movember to Make a Difference for Men's Health Worldwide
09 November, 2020
Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week Russia: Intercity experiment and TikTok reality show
02 November, 2020
5 Cybersecurity Tips for Fashion Business Owners
29 October, 2020
Fashion retailer Gap will close all company-owned stores in Europe
26 October, 2020
Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week Russia with offline and online presentations
26 October, 2020
Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week Russia presents 60 designers and fashion houses
Euratex calls for a modern and competitive Textiles and Clothing industry
02 October, 2020
Mercedes-Benz Fashion Week Russia will take place on October 20-24 in a brand-new format
25 September, 2020
The 10 Finalists of Reimagine Fashion: Changing behaviours for sustainable fashion
Premiére Vision Paris cancels the physical edition of its show and reinforces digital show
31 August, 2020
Global Talents Digital is looking for sustainable emerging designers from all over the world
ELIIT Project - the first 15 selected partnerships are announced
08 July, 2020
Euratex presented the strategy for the future of the European textile and clothing industry
26 June, 2020
Munich Fabric Start and Bluezone will take place from 1 – 3 September 2020
17 June, 2020
10 Million Views of Global Talents Digital in Social Media
15 June, 2020
Cmmn Swdn Officially Opens Paris Men's Fashion Week S/S 2019
26 June, 2018
Balmain's Homme Vision of Rock Glam '19 at Paris Men's Fashion Week
